<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smyth Lab at WEHI Bioinformatics</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Smyth Lab at WEHI Bioinformatics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-au</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Help Page</title><link>/faqs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/faqs/</guid><description>FAQ page is coming soon.</description></item><item><title>Lab Members</title><link>/people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/people/</guid><description>
Prof Gordon Smyth
Lab Head, Joint Division Head Dr Pedro Baldoni
Postdoctoral Fellow Dr Yunshun Chen
Postdoctoral Fellow Dr Hannah Coughlan
Postdoctoral Fellow Research Students Jinming Cheng PhD Student Mengbo Li PhD Student Ilariya Tarasova PhD Student</description></item><item><title>Popular software</title><link>/resources/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/resources/</guid><description>limma: Linear Models for Microarray Data Limma is an R package for the analysis of gene expression microarray data, especially the use of linear models for analysing designed experiments and the assessment of differential expression. Limma provides the ability to analyse comparisons between many RNA targets simultaneously in arbitrary complicated designed experiments. Empirical Bayesian methods are used to provide stable results even when the number of arrays is small.</description></item><item><title>Recent publications</title><link>/publications/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/publications/</guid><description>†: Equal contribution. 2021 Aug Conditionally accepted on 2 August Zhan Y, Zhang Y, Zhang S, Coughlan H, Baldoni PL, Jacquelot N, Cao WJH, Preston S, Louis C, Rautela J, Pellegrini M, Wicks IP, Alexander WS, Harrison LC, Lew AM, Smyth GK, Nutt SL, Chopin M (2021). Differential requirement for the Polycomb Repressor Complex 2 in dendritic cells and tissue resident myeloid cells. Science Immunology</description></item></channel></rss>